// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the maximum length of a Python identifier?",
    answer: "No fixed Length is specified",
    options: [
      "32",
      "16",
      "128",
      "No fixed Length is specified"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "print(2**3 + (5 + 6)**(1 + 1))",
    answer: "129",
    options: [
      "129",
      "8",
      "121",
      "None of the Above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "How is a code block indicated in Python?",
    answer: "Indentation",
    options: [
      "Brackets",
      "Indentation",
      "Key",
      "None of the Above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What does SQL stand for?",
    answer: "Structured Query Language",
    options: [
      "Stylish Question Language",
      "Stylesheet Query Language",
      "Statement Question Language",
      "Structured Query Language"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following concepts is not a part of Python?",
    answer: "Pointers",
    options: [
      "Loops",
      "Dynamic Typing",
      "Pointers",
      "All of the Above"
    ]
  },
  {
    num: 6,
    question: "In which language is Python written?",
    answer: "C",
    options: [
        "C++",
        "C",
        "Java",
        "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    num: 7,
    question: "What will be the result of the following expression in Python “2 ** 3 + 5 ** 2”?",
    answer: "33",
    options: [
        "65536",
        "33",
        "169",
        "None of the above"

    ]
  },
  {
    num: 8,
    question:"Which of the following are valid string manipulation functions in Python?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options:[
        "count()",
        "upper()",
        "strip()",
        "All of the above"
    ]

  },
  {
    num: 9,
    question: "Which of the following is not a valid set operation in python?",
    answer: "None of the Above",
    options:[
        "Union",
        "Intersection",
        "Difference",
        "None of the Above"
    ]

  },
  {
    num: 10,
    question: "As what datatype are the *kwargs stored, when passed into a function?",
    answer: "Dictionary",
    options:[
        "Dictionary",
        "List",
        "Tuple",
        "None of the above"

    ]

  }
  
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];